When did I fall asleep?
ฉันเผลอหลับไปตอนไหน
Miss Voice-from-the-Sky.
นางสาววอยซ์จากฟ้า
You should have told me that I would lose conscious during evolution.
คุณน่าจะบอกฉันว่าฉันจะหมดสติระหว่างวิวัฒนาการ
Is the evolution over?
วิวัฒนาการสิ้นสุดลงหรือไม่?
But it seems my appearance hasn't changed much.
แต่ดูเหมือนว่ารูปลักษณ์ของฉันไม่ได้เปลี่ยนไปมากนัก
I should identify now.
ฉันควรจะระบุตอนนี้
SMALL TARATECT. NAMELESS.
ทาราเทกขนาดเล็ก นิรนาม
The species name has changed. I think it was successful.
เปลี่ยนชื่อสายพันธุ์แล้ว ฉันคิดว่ามันประสบความสำเร็จ
"LEVEL ONE: WEAK" But...
"ระดับหนึ่ง: อ่อนแอ" แต่...
Level one?
ระดับหนึ่ง?
That means I have to start from level one again once I've evolved?
นั่นหมายความว่าฉันต้องเริ่มต้นจากระดับหนึ่งอีกครั้งเมื่อฉันพัฒนาแล้ว?
My stamina is almost up.
ความอดทนของฉันใกล้จะเต็มแล้ว
That's the reason.
นั่นคือเหตุผล.
I have been feeling tired and hungry since just now.
ฉันรู้สึกเหนื่อยและหิวตั้งแต่ตอนนี้
I'm so hungry yet this is so nasty.
ฉันหิวมาก แต่นี่มันน่ารังเกียจมาก
But I must recover first.
แต่ฉันต้องพักฟื้นก่อน
I want to eat. I want to eat it.
ฉันต้องการที่จะกิน ฉันต้องการที่จะกินมัน
In order to survive.
เพื่อที่จะเอาตัวรอด
I eat very little in my previous life.
ฉันกินน้อยมากในชีวิตก่อนหน้าของฉัน
And now I have to be a greedy eater.
และตอนนี้ฉันต้องเป็นนักกินตะกละ
If I were to join an eating competition now,
ถ้าฉันจะเข้าร่วมการแข่งขันกินตอนนี้
I will surely win.
ฉันจะชนะอย่างแน่นอน
I still can eat.
ฉันยังกินได้
Seriously? I'm just 80% full after eating so much.
อย่างจริงจัง? ฉันแค่ 80% อิ่มหลังจากกินมาก
Evolution is tiring.
วิวัฒนาการเป็นสิ่งที่น่าเบื่อหน่าย
Okay. Since I've done eating,
ตกลง. ตั้งแต่กินข้าวเสร็จ
I have no reason to keep staying here.
ฉันไม่มีเหตุผลที่จะต้องอยู่ที่นี่ต่อไป
I shall step onto the next journey to find prey.
ฉันจะก้าวไปสู่การเดินทางต่อไปเพื่อค้นหาเหยื่อ
I have slept and eaten enough.
ฉันนอนหลับและกินเพียงพอ
Thank you for letting me recover for now.
ขอบคุณที่ให้ฉันฟื้นตัวในตอนนี้
I shall go now.
ฉันจะไปเดี๋ยวนี้
Goodbye.
ลาก่อน
EPISODE 3: EARTH DRAGON, BAD NEWS?
ตอนที่ 3: EARTH DRAGON ข่าวร้าย?
♫Looking at the end of the entangled karma♫
♫มองที่จุดสิ้นสุดของกรรมที่พันกัน♫
♫Even my back is full of enemies♫
♫แม้แต่แผ่นหลังของฉันก็ยังเต็มไปด้วยศัตรู♫
♫Thousand of creatures♫
♫ สิ่งมีชีวิตนับพัน ♫
♫who are arrogant and ready to charge♫
♫ที่หยิ่งทะนงและพร้อมที่จะชาร์จ♫
♫Dive for alive♫
♫ดำน้ำเพื่อชีวิต♫
♫Climb for life♫
♫ไต่เขาเพื่อชีวิต♫
♫A chaotic state that no one can survive♫
♫สภาวะที่ไม่มีใครสามารถอยู่รอดได้♫
♫Take this as my stage♫
♫ใช้นี้เป็นเวทีของฉัน♫
♫Is this over?♫
♫ จบแล้วเหรอ ♫
♫But I'm not done♫
♫แต่ฉันยังไม่เสร็จ♫
♫Even if you didn't see the fatal silk♫
♫ถึงจะไม่เห็นไหมมรณะก็ตาม♫
♫you'll be eaten by me if you fall into the web♫
♫เธอจะถูกกินโดยฉันถ้าคุณตกลงไปในเว็บ♫
♫Deeper... inside♫
♫ลึก...ข้างใน♫
♫Spider pride made a cruel mark♫
♫ความภาคภูมิใจของแมงมุมสร้างรอยอันโหดร้าย♫
♫in this chest again♫
♫ในอกนี้อีกครั้ง♫
♫Finding the perfect way isn't enough♫
♫การหาทางที่สมบูรณ์แบบไม่เพียงพอ♫
♫The shredded life must be reformed♫
♫ชีวิตที่แหลกสลายต้องปฏิรูป♫
♫Think desperately♫
♫คิดอย่างสิ้นหวัง♫
♫Fight desperately♫
♫ต่อสู้อย่างสิ้นหวัง♫
♫The so-called reality. Feel a bit cold♫
♫สิ่งที่เรียกว่าความจริง รู้สึกหนาวเล็กน้อย ♫
♫Keep living the spider way♫
♫ ใช้ชีวิตตามวิถีแมงมุม ♫
♫Wait and see♫
♫รอดูกันต่อไป♫
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT?
ฉันเป็นแมงมุม แล้วไง
SILK CONTROL. INVESTIGATION.
การควบคุมไหม ตรวจสอบ.
These are the only two skills I can have now.
นี่เป็นเพียงสองทักษะที่ฉันสามารถมีได้ในตอนนี้
Silk control is about controlling silks, I supposed?
การควบคุมไหมเป็นเรื่องเกี่ยวกับการควบคุมไหม ฉันคิดว่า?
It's an essential for me whose main force is the spider silks.
สิ่งสำคัญสำหรับฉันคือใยแมงมุม
If I can improve my silk control skill,
ถ้าฉันสามารถพัฒนาทักษะการควบคุมไหม
one day...
วันหนึ่ง...
I can also be like my good neighbour in New York.
ฉันสามารถเป็นเหมือนเพื่อนบ้านที่ดีของฉันในนิวยอร์กได้เช่นกัน
Using my spider silks gracefully.
ใช้ใยแมงมุมของฉันอย่างสง่างาม
And this one...
และอันนี้...
This is the one, investigation.
นี่คือหนึ่งการสอบสวน
I can find out the existence of enemies in advance.
ฉันสามารถค้นหาการมีอยู่ของศัตรูล่วงหน้า
It's an important strategy skill.
เป็นทักษะกลยุทธ์ที่สำคัญ
Okay. I want both of them.
ตกลง. ฉันต้องการทั้งคู่
Please obtain the silk control and investigation skills with your points.
โปรดรับทักษะการควบคุมไหมและการสืบสวนด้วยคะแนนของคุณ
Great! Let's start investigating.
เยี่ยมมาก! มาเริ่มสืบสวนกันเลย
It hurts! What's going on?
มันเจ็บ! เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
It hurts! My head is exploding!
มันเจ็บ! หัวจะระเบิด!
Stop it now!
หยุดมันเดี๋ยวนี้!
What's with this horrible headache?
ปวดหัวอะไรขนาดนี้
I have decided
ฉันได้ตัดสินใจ
that the investigation skill
ว่าทักษะการสืบสวน
shall be permanently sealed temporarily.
จะถูกปิดผนึกอย่างถาวรชั่วคราว
Okay, next!
โอเค ต่อไป!
Silk controlling skill.
ทักษะการควบคุมไหม
Wow, the silks move so quickly.
ว้าว ผ้าไหมเคลื่อนไหวเร็วมาก
If I keep improving this skill,
ถ้าฉันพัฒนาทักษะนี้ไปเรื่อยๆ
I can surely have more uses of it.
ฉันสามารถใช้งานได้มากขึ้นอย่างแน่นอน
A spider-silk protective suit or something similar.
ชุดป้องกันไหมใยแมงมุมหรืออะไรทำนองนั้น
My dreams become bigger.
ความฝันของฉันยิ่งใหญ่ขึ้น
Enemy.
ศัตรู.
Jump!
กระโดด!
Is my enemy there?
ศัตรูของฉันอยู่ที่นั่นไหม
I lied to you!
ฉันโกหกคุณ!
Upgrade from level one to two.
อัปเกรดจากระดับหนึ่งเป็นสอง
Hooray!
ไชโย!
Proficiency achieved a certain level.
ความสามารถบรรลุระดับหนึ่ง
Identification skill upgraded to level six.
ทักษะการระบุตัวตนอัพเกรดเป็นระดับหก
Identification skill is upgraded.
ทักษะการระบุตัวตนได้รับการอัพเกรด
Assuming the upper limit of the level is ten,
สมมติว่าขีด จำกัด บนของระดับคือสิบ
there must surely be a lot of useful functions.
จะต้องมีฟังก์ชั่นที่มีประโยชน์มากมายอย่างแน่นอน
I assume.
ผมถือว่า.
Miss Identification, tell me.
Miss Identification บอกฉันที
LEVEL TWO SMALL TARATECT. NAMELESS.
ระดับที่สอง TARATECT ขนาดเล็ก นิรนาม
What is this? Great!
นี่คืออะไร? เยี่ยมมาก!
The speed shows 348. This is awesome!
ความเร็วแสดง 348 มันยอดเยี่ยมมาก!
This must be the so-called ability values.
นี่จะต้องเป็นสิ่งที่เรียกว่าค่าความสามารถ
It should be. I can finally see the ability values.
มันควรจะเป็น. ในที่สุดฉันก็เห็นค่าความสามารถ
I must find something to eat first.
ฉันต้องหาอะไรกินก่อน
Level upgrade is awesome.
การอัปเกรดระดับนั้นยอดเยี่ยมมาก
These monsters are no longer my opponent.
สัตว์ประหลาดเหล่านี้ไม่ใช่คู่ต่อสู้ของฉันอีกต่อไป
Those in front of me are not my enemy.
ผู้ที่อยู่ข้างหน้าฉันไม่ใช่ศัตรูของฉัน
I have a bad hunch.
ฉันมีลางสังหรณ์ที่ไม่ดี
It's not in front of me, it's behind!
ไม่ได้อยู่ข้างหน้า มันอยู่ข้างหลัง!
And they obviously are coming for me.
และเห็นได้ชัดว่าพวกเขากำลังมาหาฉัน
But the evolved me
แต่ตัวฉันที่วิวัฒนาการมา
won't be defeated so easily.
จะไม่แพ้ง่ายๆ
First, identify.
ขั้นแรกให้ระบุ
"HUMAN. LEVEL 29. NAME: GORDON." Human. Level 29. Named Gordon.
"มนุษย์ ระดับ 29 ชื่อ: กอร์ดอน" มนุษย์. ระดับ 29 ชื่อกอร์ดอน
"FAIL TO IDENTIFY ABILITY VALUES" Fail to identify ability values.
"ล้มเหลวในการระบุค่าความสามารถ" ล้มเหลวในการระบุค่าความสามารถ
How can I beat them, silly?
ฉันจะเอาชนะพวกเขาได้อย่างไร โง่?
They're level 29. There's no way I can beat them.
พวกเขาอยู่ที่ระดับ 29 ไม่มีทางที่ฉันจะเอาชนะพวกเขาได้
Seriously?
อย่างจริงจัง?
Such a sudden encounter. How can I beat them?
ที่จู่ๆ ก็เจอแบบนี้ ฉันจะเอาชนะพวกเขาได้อย่างไร
There's a snake ahead and humans behind.
มีงูอยู่ข้างหน้าและมนุษย์อยู่ข้างหลัง
How can I take such attacks from both sides?
ฉันจะรับการโจมตีจากทั้งสองฝ่ายได้อย่างไร?
Why are they chasing me?
ทำไมพวกเขาถึงไล่ตามฉัน?
My speed is 348.
ความเร็วของฉันคือ 348
They're so quick. Oh no!
พวกมันเร็วมาก ไม่นะ!
Humans are scarier than I thought.
มนุษย์น่ากลัวกว่าที่ฉันคิด
Help me!
ช่วยฉันด้วย!
And there are three monsters at such moment.
และมีสัตว์ประหลาดสามตัวในขณะนั้น
I have no way to run at all.
ฉันไม่มีทางวิ่งได้เลย
What should I do? I have no time to hesitate.
ฉันควรทำอย่างไรดี? ฉันไม่มีเวลาที่จะลังเล
Just give it a go.
เพียงแค่ให้มันไป
Success! I have succeeded.
สำเร็จ! ฉันทำสำเร็จแล้ว
This is the sudden explosive force when fleeing.
This is the sudden explosive force when fleeing.
The best trick, rock climbing, has succeeded.
The best trick, rock climbing, has succeeded.
What's going on?
What's going on?
Although I don't know what's going on,
Although I don't know what's going on,
I'm sorry, three passer-by monsters.
I'm sorry, three passer-by monsters.
This is the fate of survival of the fittest.
This is the fate of survival of the fittest.
You must be sacrificed in my place.
You must be sacrificed in my place.
I will pray for you. Weird.
I will pray for you. Weird.
Hold on. I can't stop.
Hold on. I can't stop.
Here you go.
Here you go.
Sorry, brother.
Sorry, brother.
Sue, you're learning so seriously. Impressive.
Sue, you're learning so seriously. Impressive.
Yes, brother.
Yes, brother.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm so sleepy.
Excuse me, that's my seat.
Excuse me, that's my seat.
History and theory of magic and so on. I really can't listen to these boring things anymore.
History and theory of magic and so on. I really can't listen to these boring things anymore.
Sorry. There's an empty seat over there.
Sorry. There's an empty seat over there.
But that's my seat.
But that's my seat.
Natsume...
Natsume...
He's exactly like how he was in the previous life.
He's exactly like how he was in the previous life.
I can't stand him.
I can't stand him.
Everyone, please take your sword
Everyone, please take your sword
and gather at the forest in the west.
and gather at the forest in the west.
Isn't this class about the introduction to magic?
Isn't this class about the introduction to magic?
It seems there's a practical lesson today.
ดูเหมือนว่าวันนี้จะมีบทเรียนเชิงปฏิบัติ
That's only right.
ถูกต้องเท่านั้น
We won't know our true strength without practical fights.
เราจะไม่รู้จักความแข็งแกร่งที่แท้จริงของเราหากไม่มีการต่อสู้เชิงปฏิบัติ
It seems he sees you as his opponent.
ดูเหมือนว่าเขาจะมองว่าคุณเป็นคู่ต่อสู้ของเขา
I guess so.
ฉันเดาอย่างนั้น
What's going on?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
No, nothing.
ไม่มีอะไร.
If you have any trouble, you should listen to the sound of God.
หากคุณมีปัญหาใด ๆ คุณควรฟังเสียงของพระเจ้า
What?
อะไร?
I heard the sound of God this morning too.
ฉันได้ยินเสียงของพระเจ้าเมื่อเช้านี้ด้วย
Once the level is upgraded,
เมื่อระดับได้รับการอัพเกรด
I can surely hear the sound of God day and night.
แน่นอนฉันสามารถได้ยินเสียงของพระเจ้าทั้งกลางวันและกลางคืน
Let's go.
ไปกันเถอะ.
The forest in the west is quite some distance from here.
ป่าทางทิศตะวันตกอยู่ห่างจากที่นี่ค่อนข้างไกล
Here, your sword.
ที่นี่ดาบของคุณ
I think she has gone through a lot as well.
ฉันคิดว่าเธอผ่านอะไรมามากมายเช่นกัน
Didn't hesitate to comfort brother.
ไม่เกรงใจน้องเลย
You're a prince indeed.
คุณเป็นเจ้าชายจริงๆ
It's unlike the school supplies. What a stylish sword.
ไม่เหมือนอุปกรณ์การเรียน ช่างเป็นดาบที่มีสไตล์
Your sword is very stylish too, Hugo.
ดาบของคุณก็มีสไตล์เช่นกัน ฮิวโก้
However, the inner beauty is more important than the outer.
อย่างไรก็ตาม ความงามภายในสำคัญกว่าภายนอก
Yamada.
ยามาดะ.
He's Schlain Zagan Analeit,
เขาคือชเลน ซากัน อานาเลต
the prince of the Kingdom of Analeit.
เจ้าชายแห่งอาณาจักรอนาเลต
That was rude of me, Prince Schlain.
นั่นเป็นคำหยาบคายของฉัน เจ้าชายชเลน
How dare you be so rude to my brother?
กล้าดียังไงมาหยาบคายกับพี่
Sue.
ฟ้อง.
Natsume...
นัตสึเมะ...
It's Hugo Baint Renxandt.
มันคือ Hugo Baint Renxandt
That's the right name, Your Highness.
นั่นเป็นชื่อที่ถูกต้อง ฝ่าบาท
There are people watching here.
มีคนดูอยู่นี่
You should call him by his name here.
คุณควรเรียกเขาด้วยชื่อของเขาที่นี่
Okay, sorry.
โอเคขอโทษ.
Everyone, please get a magic wand each.
ทุกคน โปรดรับไม้กายสิทธิ์คนละอัน
We're going to use the magic wands we just distributed
เราจะใช้ไม้กายสิทธิ์ที่เราเพิ่งแจกจ่ายไป
to carry out the practical class.
เพื่อดำเนินการเรียนภาคปฏิบัติ
For safety reasons,
ด้วยเหตุผลด้านความปลอดภัย
we're using magic wands filled with Water Magic.
เราใช้ไม้กายสิทธิ์ที่เต็มไปด้วยเวทแห่งน้ำ
Water?
น้ำ?
To have the ability of magic induction and magic control.
ให้มีความสามารถในการเหนี่ยวนำเวทย์มนต์และการควบคุมเวทย์มนตร์
Yes.
ใช่.
Focus your magic power
เน้นพลังเวทย์มนตร์ของคุณ
and focus it on the magic wand.
และมุ่งความสนใจไปที่ไม้กายสิทธิ์
Each one of you shoot a water bomb towards the target.
คุณแต่ละคนยิงระเบิดน้ำไปที่เป้าหมาย
Remember, never target others.
จำไว้ว่าอย่ากำหนดเป้าหมายผู้อื่น
Please beware of how much magic power you have left.
โปรดระวังพลังเวทย์มนตร์ที่คุณเหลืออยู่
I won't be responsible if you faint trying to flaunt your superiority.
ฉันจะไม่รับผิดชอบถ้าคุณหน้ามืดพยายามที่จะอวดความเหนือกว่าของคุณ
So irresponsible.
ไร้ความรับผิดชอบเลย
What was that?
เมื่อกี้คืออะไร?
Fei, you scared everyone. Don't do that.
เฟ คุณกลัวทุกคน อย่าทำอย่างนั้น
You're just talking, yet you didn't hit the target even once.
คุณแค่พูดไป คุณยังไม่ถึงเป้าหมายเลยแม้แต่ครั้งเดียว
Water Magic?
มายากลน้ำ?
I hope we could practise Earth Magic instead.
ฉันหวังว่าเราจะได้ฝึก Earth Magic แทน
Fei is an earth dragon.
เฟเป็นมังกรดิน
You must be very good in Earth Magic.
คุณต้องเก่งมากใน Earth Magic
Even when I've practised very powerful magic,
แม้ว่าฉันจะฝึกเวทย์มนตร์ที่ทรงพลังมาก
it will go to waste without usage.
มันจะไปเสียเปล่าโดยไม่ต้องใช้
Don't worry.
ไม่ต้องกังวล
The school has magic tools that can be used for all kinds of magic.
โรงเรียนมีเครื่องมือวิเศษที่สามารถใช้เวทมนตร์ได้ทุกประเภท
I'm not good in using water,
ฉันใช้น้ำไม่เก่ง
but better in using fire.
แต่ใช้ไฟได้ดีกว่า
What a coincidence. I'm better in using fire than water as well.
ช่างเป็นเรื่องบังเอิญ ฉันใช้ไฟได้ดีกว่าน้ำด้วย
Level upgrade...
อัพเลเวล...
Is it okay for her to shoot like that?
มันโอเคสำหรับเธอที่จะยิงแบบนั้น?
Alright, Oka...
โอเค โอเค...
Oh no, Filimøs isn't here again?
ไม่นะ Filimøs ไม่อยู่แล้วเหรอ?
Yes. She's always absent in class.
ใช่. เธอไม่อยู่ในชั้นเรียนเสมอ
I wonder what she's doing.
ฉันสงสัยว่าเธอกำลังทำอะไร
She'll just ignore me if I ask.
เธอจะไม่สนใจฉันถ้าฉันถาม
Out of energy? You have no perseverance.
พลังงานหมด? คุณไม่มีความเพียร
Sue, are you not going to practise?
ซู คุณจะไม่ฝึกเหรอ?
Seeing how these trash are astonished by your perfect magic
เมื่อเห็นว่าขยะเหล่านี้ประหลาดใจกับเวทมนตร์ที่สมบูรณ์แบบของคุณอย่างไร perfect
and how they adore you is my happiest moment.
และวิธีที่พวกเขารักคุณคือช่วงเวลาที่มีความสุขที่สุดของฉัน
I will practise secretly later.
ฉันจะฝึกฝนอย่างลับๆในภายหลัง
Level upgrade...
อัพเลเวล...
In order to hear the sound of God.
เพื่อที่จะได้ยินเสียงของพระเจ้า
-She's working very hard to upgrade her level. -Level upgrade...
-เธอทำงานอย่างหนักเพื่ออัพเกรดระดับของเธอ - อัพเกรดระดับ...
Look at her.
มองที่เธอ.
Brother, so powerful. Crack shot.
แรงมากพี่ ยิงแตก.
She's good in Light and Water Magic after all.
เธอเก่งเรื่อง Light and Water Magic
Brother is perfect.
พี่ชายที่สมบูรณ์แบบ
I don't have to practise magic that I'm not good at.
ฉันไม่ต้องฝึกเวทย์มนตร์ที่ฉันไม่เก่ง
It's more efficient to practise the field that I'm good in.
การฝึกภาคสนามที่ฉันถนัดจะมีประสิทธิภาพมากกว่า
That fellow has obtained the skill of Fire Magic?
เพื่อนคนนั้นได้รับสกิล Fire Magic?
Magic is only useful at such level.
เวทย์มนตร์มีประโยชน์ในระดับนั้นเท่านั้น
I can't upgrade my level anymore.
ฉันไม่สามารถอัพเกรดระดับของฉันอีกต่อไป
This is the best time to show your strength.
นี่เป็นเวลาที่ดีที่สุดที่จะแสดงความแข็งแกร่งของคุณ
But he has gone too far.
แต่เขาไปไกลเกินไป
I admit that you have actual strength.
ฉันยอมรับว่าคุณมีความแข็งแกร่งจริงๆ
But showing off like that is not praise-worthy.
แต่การอวดเช่นนั้นไม่สมควรสรรเสริญ
Hugo.
ฮิวโก้
Is that so?
อย่างนั้นหรือ?
This is not a battlefield. This is the learning field of the school.
นี่ไม่ใช่สนามรบ นี่คือสนามการเรียนรู้ของโรงเรียน
Pick up your magic wand.
หยิบไม้กายสิทธิ์ขึ้นมา
Who knows when this will turn into a battlefield?
ใครจะรู้เมื่อสิ่งนี้จะกลายเป็นสนามรบ?
This guy...
ผู้ชายคนนี้...
He's exactly like how he was in the previous life.
เขาเป็นเหมือนอย่างที่เขาเป็นในชีวิตก่อนหน้านี้
He's even worse than before.
เขาเลวร้ายยิ่งกว่าเดิม
What's going on?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
Didn't you hear that?
ไม่ได้ยินเหรอ?
What?
อะไร?
Retreat!
ล่าถอย!
Teacher!
ครู!
It's coming.
มันกำลังมา.
It's earth dragon.
มันคือมังกรดิน
Awesome!
เจ๋ง!
It's finally my time to perform.
ในที่สุดก็ถึงเวลาแสดงของฉันแล้ว
Watch!
ดู!
I can deal with this fellow easily with my power.
ฉันสามารถจัดการกับเพื่อนคนนี้ได้อย่างง่ายดายด้วยพลังของฉัน
No! Come back!
ไม่! กลับมา!
I'll burn you down.
ฉันจะเผาคุณ
What?
อะไร?
It neutralised magic.
มันทำให้เวทมนตร์เป็นกลาง
It's the skill of a imperial wrath.
เป็นทักษะแห่งความโกรธเกรี้ยวของจักรพรรดิ
Are you kidding me?
คุณล้อเล่นหรือเปล่า
Another strike!
ตีอีก!
Hugo!
ฮิวโก้!
Killed?
ฆ่า?
Is this death?
นี่คือความตาย?
Julius.
จูเลียส
Brother.
พี่ชาย.
At such moment, Brother Julius
ในขณะนั้น พี่จูเลียส
will surely fight bravely!
จะสู้อย่างกล้าหาญอย่างแน่นอน!
Brother.
พี่ชาย.
Shun.
ชุน
We'll all die if this goes on.
พวกเราจะตายกันหมดถ้าเป็นเช่นนี้
Fei, take care of Sue.
เฟ ดูแลซู
Shun.
ชุน
Katia. Yuri.
คาเทีย. ยูริ.
There's no other way.
ไม่มีทางอื่น
God would want us to fight together.
พระเจ้าต้องการให้เราต่อสู้ด้วยกัน
Brother.
พี่ชาย.
Sue, retreat!
ซู ถอย!
Hold on! Stop!
เดี๋ยวก่อน! หยุด!
Don't come along.
อย่ามาเลย
No.
เลขที่
I want to come with you.
ฉันต้องการที่จะมากับคุณ
Run!
วิ่ง!
Good. Sue, Yuri.
ดี. ซู, ยูริ.
Cooperate with me.
ร่วมมือกับฉัน
Okay.
ตกลง.
Bres, retreat.
เบรส ถอยไป
Those behind us will be hit if you keep going.
คนข้างหลังเราจะโดนโจมตีถ้าคุณไปต่อ
Magic power.
อำนาจวิเศษ.
Air power.
พลังงานลม
Magic of Light?
เวทมนตร์แห่งแสง?
Brother!
พี่!
Get off!
ลง!
Stop! You may hit Sue and the rest.
หยุด! คุณอาจตีซูและส่วนที่เหลือ
That's why I told you to get off.
นั่นเป็นเหตุผลที่ฉันบอกคุณให้ลง
You silly!
คุณโง่!
Oh my.
พุทโธ่.
A bunch of overconfident lads.
กลุ่มคนที่มีความมั่นใจมากเกินไป
Fei.
เฟย
Brother.
พี่ชาย.
Are you okay?
คุณสบายดีไหม?
Are you injured?
คุณได้รับบาดเจ็บหรือไม่?
I'm fine.
ฉันสบายดี.
You saved us.
คุณช่วยเรา
Thank you, Fei.
ขอบคุณเฟย
Respond to everyone's cheering.
ตอบรับเสียงเชียร์ของทุกคน
It seems there's one person who's not grateful.
ดูเหมือนว่ามีคนหนึ่งที่ไม่ขอบคุณ
Fei, what's going on?
เฟย เป็นอะไรไป?
Try identifying me.
ลองระบุตัวฉัน
Identify?
แยกแยะ?
CANNIBAL.
มนุษย์กินคน
Cannibal?
มนุษย์กินคน?
Seriously?
อย่างจริงจัง?
Just like what you thought.
เหมือนกับที่คุณคิด
This is your parent?
นี่คือพ่อแม่ของคุณ?
Brother.
พี่ชาย.
-Shun. -Are you alright?
-ชุน -คุณสบายดีหรือเปล่า?
-Brother.
-ชุน -พี่ชาย.
-Come on, Shun. -Brother, get up.
- เอาล่ะชุน - พี่ชายลุกขึ้น
Shun.
ชุน
-Shun. -Brother.
-ชุน -พี่ชาย.
Do you know? This is the prelude.
คุณรู้หรือไม่? นี่คือโหมโรง
The life of a spider.
ชีวิตของแมงมุม
I'm going to start singing.
ฉันจะเริ่มร้องเพลง
♫Ordinary♫
♫ธรรมดา♫
♫High school girl♫
♫ สาวมัธยม ♫
♫Ancient literature♫
♫วรรณกรรมโบราณ♫
♫Class♫
♫คลาส♫
♫Suddenly destroyed♫
♫ จู่ ๆ ก็ถูกทำลาย ♫
♫Time♫
♫เวลา♫
♫Process♫
♫กระบวนการ♫
♫Awareness♫
♫การรับรู้♫
♫Conscious♫
♫มีสติ♫
♫Became a spider♫
♫กลายเป็นแมงมุม♫
♫So confusing♫
♫ สับสนจัง ♫
♫Running here and there in chaos, little spider♫
♫วิ่งไปโน่นไปนี่ด้วยความโกลาหล เจ้าแมงมุมตัวน้อย♫
♫Being helpless in this big labyrinth♫
♫ อยู่ลำพังในเขาวงกตใหญ่นี้ ♫
♫Working hard to survive as the fittest, little spider♫
♫ทำงานหนักเพื่อเอาตัวรอดอย่างแมงมุมตัวน้อยที่แข็งแรงที่สุด♫
♫I'll just tell you. My power was weak at the beginning♫
♫ฉันจะบอกคุณ พลังของฉันอ่อนแอในตอนเริ่มต้น♫
♫Tricky enemies♫
♫ศัตรูเจ้าเล่ห์♫
♫Horrible food♫
♫อาหารที่น่ากลัว♫
♫Sweat and tears. What a misfortune♫
♫ทั้งหยาดเหงื่อและน้ำตา ช่างโชคร้ายเหลือเกิน♫
♫Don't give up even if your house is burnt down♫
♫อย่าท้อถอยแม้บ้านจะถูกไฟไหม้ ♫
♫But my heart wants my house back♫
♫แต่หัวใจอยากได้บ้านกลับคืนมา♫
♫A dream-like Isekai world of reincarnation♫
♫โลกแห่งการกลับชาติมาเกิดที่เหมือนฝันของอิเซไก♫
♫Needless to be said, the successful people♫
♫ไม่จำเป็นต้องพูดคนที่ประสบความสำเร็จ♫
♫are reincarnated as beautiful women♫
♫ได้กลับชาติมาเกิดเป็นสาวงาม♫
♫What? There's no skill that can turn things back?♫
♫อะไร? ไม่มีทักษะใดที่สามารถย้อนกลับได้ ♫
♫Identify. Spin silk. Toss. Shoot♫
♫ระบุ ปั่นไหม. โยน. ยิง♫
♫Focus. Be patient. Eat. Hide. Dodge♫
♫โฟกัส อดทน กิน. ซ่อน. ดอดจ์♫
♫Powerful silk. Venom synthesis. Drugs synthesis♫
♫ผ้าไหมทรงพลัง การสังเคราะห์พิษ การสังเคราะห์ยา♫
♫Gaido attack. Corrosive attack♫
♫ไกโดโจมตี การโจมตีที่กัดกร่อน♫
♫Various evil eyes. Final magic. Multiple avatars♫
♫ตาชั่วร้ายต่างๆ มายากลขั้นสุดท้าย อวตารหลายตัว♫
♫The final skill is to self destroy♫
♫ทักษะสุดท้ายคือการทำลายตัวเอง♫
♫Bring it on♫
♫มาเลย♫
♫I can do anything♫
♫ฉันทำได้ทุกอย่าง♫
♫Just go on if there's no other way♫
♫ไปเถอะถ้าไม่มีทางอื่น♫
♫Use all kind of skills♫
♫ใช้ทักษะทุกประเภท♫
♫I don't care even if I'm destroyed♫
♫ฉันไม่สนแม้ตัวฉันจะถูกทำลายก็ตาม♫
♫I don't want to die♫
♫ฉันยังไม่อยากตาย♫
♫I want to live♫
♫ฉันอยากมีชีวิตอยู่♫
♫I must keep living♫
♫ฉันต้องอยู่ต่อไป♫
♫Take this♫
♫ เอานี่ไป ♫
♫I don't want horrible game life♫
♫ฉันไม่ต้องการชีวิตในเกมที่น่ากลัว♫
♫Life should be better after reincarnation♫
♫ชีวิตควรจะดีขึ้นหลังจากการกลับชาติมาเกิด♫
♫Why is my beginning so miserable?♫
♫ทำไมการเริ่มต้นของฉันจึงน่าสังเวช ♫
♫I will not forgive you, admin D♫
♫ฉันจะไม่ให้อภัยคุณผู้ดูแลระบบD♫
♫The big labyrinth is just as dark today♫
♫เขาวงกตขนาดใหญ่ก็มืดมิดเหมือนวันนี้♫
♫Keep living or die trying♫
♫จงมีชีวิตอยู่หรือตายพยายามต่อไป♫
♫Although this kind of life is quite interesting♫
♫ถึงแม้ว่าชีวิตแบบนี้จะน่าสนใจทีเดียวก็ตาม♫
♫I still can't accept why♫
♫ฉันยังยอมรับไม่ได้ว่าทำไม♫
♫I am a spider♫
♫ฉันเป็นแมงมุม♫
Silk... Spider silk, come out quickly.
ไหม...ใยแมงมุมรีบออกมา
Although I didn't fall to death, it still hurt.
แม้จะไม่ได้ล้มตายแต่ก็ยังเจ็บ
This is the punishment of being on cloud nine.
นี่คือการลงโทษของการอยู่บนคลาวด์เก้า
Okay, I'll reflect on myself.
โอเค ฉันจะพิจารณาตัวเอง
I said, I will reflect on myself. Why are there more things coming?
ฉันพูดว่าฉันจะคิดทบทวนตัวเอง ทำไมยังมีของมาอีก?
FINJICOTE. LEVEL FIVE.
ฟินจิโคต ระดับห้า
Don't look my way. Let me go.
อย่ามองมาทางฉัน ปล่อยฉันไป.
Sorry.
ขอโทษ
Landed.
ลงจอด
Oh no...
ไม่นะ...
The situation is bad right now.
สถานการณ์ตอนนี้ไม่ดี
What's going on now?
เกิดอะไรขึ้นตอนนี้?
It feels like there's one disaster after another.
รู้สึกเหมือนมีภัยพิบัติครั้งแล้วครั้งเล่า
I have a bad hunch.
ฉันมีลางสังหรณ์ที่ไม่ดี
Snake.
งู.
And there are three of them.
และมีสามคน
I'm in trouble.
ฉันกำลังมีปัญหา.
It would be horrible if I were in a pincer attack again.
มันคงแย่มากถ้าฉันถูกโจมตีด้วยปากเปล่าอีกครั้ง
Great!
เยี่ยมมาก!
They're enjoying the baits.
พวกเขากำลังเพลิดเพลินกับเหยื่อ
I should take this chance to run.
ฉันควรจะใช้โอกาสนี้วิ่ง
What should this situation be called?
สถานการณ์นี้ควรเรียกว่าอะไร?
The third party is profited.
บุคคลที่สามได้กำไร
You can't have it all.
คุณไม่สามารถมีได้ทั้งหมด
They're both not right.
พวกเขาทั้งสองไม่ถูกต้อง
Whatever it is, as long as they don't find me.
ตราบใดที่พวกเขาไม่พบฉัน
The fight of monsters.
การต่อสู้ของมอนสเตอร์
"THE FIGHT OF MONSTERS" Now it's the chance to run!
"THE FIGHT OF MONSTERS" ตอนนี้ได้โอกาสวิ่งแล้ว!
"ARABA EARTH DRAGON LEVEL 31" What is this?
"ARABA EARTH DRAGON LEVEL 31" นี่อะไร?
What?
อะไร?
What is that?
นั่นคืออะไร?
Oh no!
ไม่นะ!
Oh no, run...
ไม่นะ วิ่ง...
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT? NEXT EPISODE: MONKEY, HOAR?
ฉันเป็นแมงมุม แล้วไง ตอนต่อไป: ลิง ฮอร์?
STAY TUNED
คอยติดตาม